GETAWAY AND GO WITH JANGDOBARI
I shouldn't get too excited.
Need to calm down.
One, two, three, four.
JANG DO-YEON
I need to snap out of it.
This is work.
THE THINGS THAT LIE AHEAD OF HER…
SOME BUTTERFLIES…
You're Tang Wei now.
Did I make you blush today?
Me? Of course you did.
Honey?
Honey.
We're close to Russia, so…
SOME MOMENTS OF JOY
AND SOME MOMENTS OF SHOCK
Thank you for giving me
such unforgettable memories.
LET'S BEGIN THIS UNFORGETTABLE STORY
HARBIN AIRPORT
That was fast. I thought
we'd have to wait for it to arrive.
-Taxi!
-Shall we get on the one behind?
BARIBARI
WHERE ARE WE HEADED
WITH BARIBARI BUNDLES OF STUFF?
Ever since I heard
that we would be going to Harbin,
I've been studying
some basic Mandarin phrases
that even elementary students
would understand.
Zao shang hao.
A morning greeting. "Hello."
Xiao hao. An afternoon greeting. "Hello."
Wan shang hao.
A greeting for the evening. "Hello."
Wan an.
Good night.
Wo yao pijiu.
I'd like beer, please.
DO-YEON IS A BEER LOVER
You took notes too?
"Cheers."
What are you most looking forward to
on this trip?
Looking forward to? The food.
A refreshing beer and some tasty snacks.
Love that sort of thing.
It's so delicious.
How do you feel now we're here?
Are you excited?
I had a lightbulb moment
that it's been a good while
since I've had an outdoor shoot.
Once we landed,
I saw myself at the airport,
and I was so studio-ready
with a full face of makeup.
I took a glance at my travel buddy,
and they came totally on theme
for a chill holiday,
so I felt so embarrassed.
As soon as I got to a bathroom,
I removed my falsies.
My lashes were like this.
"Hello."
They were so…
They were a little too outspoken,
so I removed them
and returned to my natural state.
I'm still getting used to things,
but I'm sure that with time,
I'll loosen up a little for our viewers.
LET'S SEE IF THAT HAPPENS
I believe so.
What are you filming?
GETAWAY AND GO WITH JANGDOBARI
EPISODE 1: HARBIN COUPLE'S HOLIDAY
WE GOT MARRIED
Hello. Bound for a breezy break
with bundles of stories in my bag.
I'm Jang Do-yeon
of Getaway and Go with Jangdobari.
JANG DO-YEON
CHEERS ALL AROUND
Everyone,
do you see this?
I'm no longer in Korea but in Harbin.
I've brought a lot of stuff,
but I won't be traveling alone
as I have a travel buddy.
This show is all about unloading
bundles of stories
and having fun with some travel buddies.
Shall we meet our buddy?
A SUSPICIOUS FIGURE IS WATCHING
If I'm to give you a clue
about this buddy of ours,
I can't remember a time
when this person hasn't been popular.
GLARING
They've always been in their prime.
And we've met before,
so we're not complete strangers,
but we're not that close,
nor are we uncomfortable.
I'm actually quite amused
that this person willingly volunteered
to join me on this show.
If I tell my friends
that this person is my first travel buddy,
I think a lot of them would be jealous.
-Hello.
-And I--
It's Byun Yo-han.
LOTS TO UNPACK
STRUGGLING
It's good to see you.
How have you been?
BYUN YO-HAN
ACTOR
I'm such a fan,
so I really wanted to meet you.
THE TWO PREVIOUSLY MET
A YEAR AGO ON SALON DRIP
I don't usually say this sort of thing,
but are you in a mood?
MOODY CHARM
I am a moody guy. Okay, cheers.
WILL PROUDLY TOAST HIMSELF
HE SHOWED ALL
OF HIS MULTI-FACETED CHARM
Did I drool just now?
You're an indescribable character.
A NEW TYPE OF CHEMISTRY
TWO HOURS AGO
It still smells the same.
It's this smell.
WHIFF
Sir?
I was a student studying abroad here
about 17 years ago.
STORY BUNDLE 1
YO-HAN DID A TWO-YEAR LANGUAGE EXCHANGE
IN HARBIN AT THE AGE OF 20
I'm in Harbin again.
It feels surreal.
A lot has changed.
I had this older friend
called Kang Min-cheol
who was studying Chinese Literature
at Korea University.
I learned from him for about three years.
STORY BUNDLE 2
MIN-CHEOL TAUGHT HIM CHINESE
IN HIGH SCHOOL
Wow.
So much has changed.
There was none of this back then.
STORY BUNDLE 3
HARBIN LOOKS SO DIFFERENT
Should I go out now?
SHOULDER BUMPS THE AUTOMATIC DOORS
SHY REUNION IN A YEAR
This isn't a prank show.
-Exactly.
-Honestly.
-I just came here as I was told.
-Yes?
But I didn't think I'd be back in Harbin.
I thought maybe I'd come back with my wife
in the future, when I'm married.
Then should we hurry to find a venue?
FLASH PROPOSAL
We could get a divorce three days later.
That sounds good.
-But no physical touch.
-Like a married couple.
I wanted to see you.
-You did?
-Yes.
But seeing you in Harbin
makes this even more special.
Right.
Earlier in the airport,
you didn't seem to know your way around.
THE PAIR WERE ON THE SAME PLANE OVER
You did study in Harbin, didn't you?
Of course I did.
SPACING OUT
Let's head inside.
I'll carry this for you.
-I've got it.
-Seriously?
-Hang on.
-It's quite heavy, isn't it?
You're too kind.
HUBBY TAKES CHARGE
The least I can do
is open the door for you.
Deary me.
Hello.
-Your passport.
-Sure.
People would think we're sharing a room.
I was only joking.
Of course.
-Would that be okay?
-Sure, fine.
I'm good too.
Me too.
The bathroom might be an issue.
We could blast music, though.
Wait, you know that trick? Blasting music.
Of course I do.
I'll leave the tap running.
ALREADY IN SYNC
Let's go.
This is great.
Please, Yo-han. I can take my own trunk.
This is hilarious.
ALL CHECKED IN TO SEPARATE ROOMS
TEEHEE
Now you've changed,
you're like a different person.
Well, talk about pot calling kettle black.
"Pot calling kettle black"?
Haven't heard that in a while.
-Get in.
-After you.
CONSIDERATE COUPLE
Look at this angle.
Isn't this angle like the one
from Director Park Chan-wook's movie?
-Decision to Leave?
-Yes.
Dead or alive, we stick together.
Of course.
Let's speak comfortably.
-Me to you?
-Yes.
What should I call you?
-Call me?
-Yes.
Nuna?
You can call me Tang Wei.
We're Korean,
so you can call me Gamja-Tang Wei.
Well, I think…
I should be Park Kale.
-Well, kale is good for you.
-It is.
And I'll be Gamja-Tang Wei.
Have you already made
the decision to leave me?
You've seen that movie?
I've even seen Following.
Following did well thanks to Salon Drip.
Come on, that's not true.
I honestly believe that.
-You do?
-Honestly.
When your new film comes out,
I'll make sure to check it out.
What's it called again?
Your World.
-Directed by Yi Ok-seop.
-Your World.
And starring actor Koo Kyo-hwan.
When I saw the stills
of these two charming people
gazing into each other's eyes,
I was totally drawn in.
Really?
I could feel your energies.
A still cut gives you
a taste of what it was like on set.
Just by looking at those stills,
I was intrigued by the film.
You were?
I think the film will be fascinating.
I'm fascinated that I'm even in a film.
The Mandarin phrases
you practiced earlier…
-What were they?
-Show him.
I'd like a beer.
That's a lovely phrase.
MOST CONFIDENT AT ORDERING BEER
That's spot on.
Just say that every day
until we leave Harbin.
I'D LIKE BEER, PLEASE
So, for our first destination…
I didn't ask, but we're getting dumplings.
My favorite.
ZHANG BAO PU
A DUMPLING JOINT IN HARBIN
WITH OVER A CENTURY'S HISTORY
-Oh boy.
-Boy.
So it's here?
For the sake of smooth travels,
shall we drop the honorifics?
Sounds good. I love it.
Yes, right. This is great.
It says it's a century old.
Yeah, it says "1902" here.
OPEN SINCE 1902
Are there seats?
Seats?
It's packed full of people.
They want us to go upstairs.
Thank you.
That looks delicious.
Are you allowed to drink?
Can you?
Would that be okay?
-Shall we pick up the honorifics again?
-Oh, I don't know.
-There's a breeze. Will you keep that on?
-Yes, I'm good.
-Give me that.
-Such a gentleman.
You are my wife.
Thank you, Park Kale.
I'm here at this famous joint
all thanks to you.
I was too broke to come as a student.
I'll pay with Alipay.
I'm so grateful.
I'll enjoy the meal.
Hello.
This is the character for "bean,"
so it must be tofu.
-Gyoza.
-Tofu.
ONE TOFU DUMPLING
ONE SMALL RIB DUMPLING
I think it's this.
ONE MAJIANG LIANGPI
I heard this one's delicious.
If there's anything you want…
Meiyou… I mean, no, I don't.
You're speaking Mandarin to me now?
Harbin is known for its beer.
-So let's go with Hapi.
-Great.
GO AHEAD
First,
we'd like two beers, please.
TWO BOTTLES OF HARBIN BEER
What type of traveler are you?
-Do you travel alone or with friends?
-You first. You?
I used to prefer traveling alone,
but I've found traveling with a friend
you click with is great.
I like how we're doing it today.
-The two of us.
-How exactly are we doing it today?
We locked eyes, then got married.
As soon as we checked in.
I love it.
Wow.
Looks good.
FIRST MENU
MAJIANG LIANGPI
KEEN EYES
Is this Harbin…
I think it is Hapi, but let me check.
-Is it what we're…
-No, this isn't it.
Excuse me?
Do you not have Hapi?
-We don't.
-You don't?
Thank you.
This is Xuehua,
a Northeastern specialty beer, apparently.
-It still looks good.
-I'll open it.
No Harbin beer?
I did understand "meiyou."
They don't have Hapi now.
-Okay.
-You understood.
-I'll pour you a glass first.
-Thank you.
RESPECTFULLY
Damn it.
-You punk.
-I'm just joking.
You're not that much younger.
-You know I'm joking, right?
-Yes.
DO-YEON, BORN IN 1985
BYUN YO-HAN, BORN IN 1986
ONLY A YEAR YOUNGER
-You're coming to life now.
-No, I was just joking.
I was kidding. You're my guest.
Thank you.
CHUGGING THEIR FIRST BEERS
It's not bitter at all.
It tastes like barley.
-Right.
-Isn't it great?
Did you have beer like this back then?
-Back in school?
-Back then, I drank Hapi.
Harbin beer.
-That's called Hapi?
-Yes.
It was everywhere back then,
so it's odd that they don't have any.
Then tell me something.
We have to hang out for the next two days.
Is there anything you don't want me to do?
There's nothing of the sort.
We're here on a trip.
Let's try everything.
Really?
I'd like you to let loose.
-I'll do the same.
-You will?
I'll ask you a question, then.
Any lines you don't want me to cross?
Any lines?
I'm fine with almost everything.
We'll be drinking a couple of glasses
of Harbin beer, right?
You know when people ask, "Are you drunk?"
-You don't want me to say that?
-Yes.
Things like "Are you drunk?"
That must be one of your pet peeves.
-It's a total buzzkill.
-I get you.
I agree with you.
You do?
"You're drunk. Go home."
No saying things like,
"You should think about tomorrow."
I hate that stuff too.
Okay.
Okay, cheers.
NO BUZZKILL TALK
MAJIANG LIANGPI
TRANSLUCENT, WIDE NOODLES
TOSSED IN A COLD, REFRESHING PEANUT SAUCE
-Shall we eat? Here.
-Yes.
NEWLYWED CHEMISTRY OFF THE CHARTS
Let's mix it
together.
We're still a little cautious.
Wait, no being cautious.
HARBIN COUPLE'S TRAVEL RULES:
NO BEING CAUTIOUS
While we're traveling.
I like it.
Let's mix.
Okay.
MIXING WITHOUT CAUTION
It smells great.
FLINCH
FLINCH22
I'm sorry. I was cautious just now
with my chopsticks.
Come on, we said no being cautious.
I know we said that,
but it was just instinctive.
Do you like spicy food?
You don't?
No, I do.
Then eat up.
-Am I acting moody?
-No.
Why would you remember that?
I found it so funny.
Are you in a mood?
Then that's a relief.
I also rather like that part
in a strange, perverted way.
SLURP
This just calls for some booze.
-It's so good.
-Right?
It's a total booze magnet.
It's delicious.
I thought it'd be like chewy rice cakes,
but it's super soft.
They're like flat glass noodles,
but a lot softer.
They're good.
NEXT MENU
DUMPLINGS
-This was so good.
-It was good.
EXPLAINING THE MENU
-Thank you.
-What did she say?
I have no clue.
Have a taste.
Eat up.
WIFE FIRST WHEN IT COMES TO DUMPLINGS
Come on.
I think these are short rib dumplings.
Sounds good.
Oh, it's tofu.
TOFU
I thought of something else
we shouldn't do.
What?
If you don't know,
you don't have to act like you know.
I'm just making an effort.
I'm giving it a guess.
Oh, she meant they'll be serving
the short rib dumplings next.
FLINCH
-Is it good?
-Yes.
That's a relief.
I'll pour you a glass.
This is meat.
-So one was…
-One was tofu, and the other was meat.
SHORT RIB DUMPLING
-How is it?
-Good.
NOD OF APPROVAL
The texture is almost like…
Like what?
WHAT DOES DO-YEON THINK
OF THE MAJIANG LIANGPI'S MOUTHFEEL?
It feels like a tongue.
What do you mean?
I have no clue.
It's super soft.
It's a little…
-The texture is…
-I'm not quite sure.
It felt like
I was eating something sacred.
You really have a way with words.
I also kept thinking,
"Why does it feel like I'm kissing?"
Why does it keep
wrapping around my tongue?
It's caressing my tongue.
ENTER MORE DUMPLINGS
Is there anywhere you've wanted to visit?
-There is.
-Where?
The places I used to go to
when I was living here.
Places I went on memorable occasions.
On my birthday,
when my friends took me out to celebrate.
There's a place called Central Street.
-Central Street?
-Yes.
What happens there?
I've heard a lot about it.
There are a lot of trendy shops there.
The night lights are pretty,
and the architecture too.
-It's pretty?
-Yes.
There are a lot of great buildings
with Eastern European influence.
I've wanted to go back.
To Central Street?
I was feeling so lonely on my birthday,
but my friends cheered me up there.
I pretended to be surprised
and shed a few tears.
I said, "What did you prepare
all this for?"
-Because you were grateful?
-Yes.
How old were you back then?
Around 20 or so?
-You were just a baby.
-Twenty or twenty-one.
This all feels so good, honestly.
Back at the airport,
I couldn't quite believe it.
It is a little bizarre, right?
It doesn't quite make sense to me.
The whole thing feels surreal.
I'd vaguely thought about
returning here with my future wife,
but I never imagined I'd be here with you.
And I never imagined
that you would get whisked away
for a Covid test.
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT…?
As soon as we got on the plane,
I completely crashed.
And once we landed,
the lady made such a charismatic entrance.
-She did.
-To do Covid tests.
As if to say, "You're all screwed."
It did feel as though
they were going to lock the doors.
The stewardesses drew the curtains,
so I thought,
"This has nothing to do with us."
Then suddenly, Do-yeon took off.
They suddenly called "Jang Do-yeon."
So I said, "That's me."
Harbin chose you, I guess.
You didn't speak any Mandarin
when you first came to study, right?
No, I came prepared.
That's it for the Mandarin talk.
I wanted to get some juicy details
about your hardships,
but let's move on to the next chapter.
Was it hard making friends at all?
Not hard, per se.
I think I…
That's all for the friend talk.
-Now, the next chapter.
-I mean, sure.
It was a definite adjustment to be abroad,
but I never felt particularly alone.
Were you dating a fellow student?
I dated, yes.
-You loved?
-Yes.
She was from Russia.
That's awesome.
-Was she also a student?
-Yes.
We dated in secret.
Why in secret?
I felt a little shy about dating,
so we would secretly meet at night,
after class, on the 16th floor.
What was on the 16th floor?
There were these researchers' labs.
I'm not saying we went in there.
We hung out on the stairs.
You did?
"How was today?"
"That's what you got up to?"
I would teach her Korean,
and she taught me some Russian.
Are you okay to talk about this?
This was almost 20 years ago,
and I'm married now, so…
MARRIED FOR AN HOUR
One glass, please.
BOWS IN SHAME
Why are you opening
the Pandora's box of my past?
So you dated a Russian woman, did you?
What matters is who I'm here with now.
That would be me.
That's what's important.
Let's not dwell on the past.
Just look straight ahead.
We have two days left.
We just got married.
To think, we'll soon be divorced.
I'm going to stay up tonight.
Let's treat a day like 100 days.
Are you kissing?
I'm sorry to do so while you're talking.
-No, please.
-Let me find some joy.
Please go ahead.
Deary me.
Don't mind…
Don't mind me.
Just do whatever you please.
I'll do it too.
Your slurping's getting louder.
PFFT
When I meet you,
I think all my senses come to life.
I start drooling.
My nose starts running.
You drive me wild.
Are we okay to air this?
It's fine with me.
I'd love for all of this to air.
I want to strip away all the facades
that I've come to wear as an actor.
Do you get me?
What sort of facades?
When I'm shooting for a commercial,
I wear my money smile.
As you should, since it's a job.
But when I'm acting
or in my day-to-day life,
I'm a believer
in stripping all of that away.
I want to wear my natural smile,
not a fake one.
From a certain point on,
I've found myself to be so curated.
I think the reason
Byun Yo-han first sparkled
was because he was oblivious
to how he was being perceived.
But that's…
With time, you gain more experience,
and although you might remember
how you used to sparkle with fondness,
others may envy you now
because you're so seasoned.
-And want to be like you.
-Right.
I'm sure a lot of people think that.
So, I…
-Sorry, a burp's coming.
-A burp?
EXHALE
This is great.
I unintentionally dropped honorifics
just now. Is that okay?
I love it. It's all good.
-Man, I'm sorry.
-You're good.
Are you getting choked up?
This is great.
I think I can say these things
because it's you.
You make me want to show my natural self.
That's what's been on my mind
the most lately.
Even just recently, when I was acting.
When you're acting…
I mean, I wouldn't know,
but the character--
-That was me talking.
-I have another rule.
Do you think you could
keep the number of burps below ten?
I won't tell you not to burp.
I'll try my absolute best.
Even if I have to gag myself.
I won't even try and sneak one
by doing a half-burp.
If I need to, I'll just let it out.
Anyway, I'll try to keep it
to less than ten.
You're hilarious.
ALREADY STRUGGLING
And…
I MUST HOLD IT IN…
REACHING HIS LIMIT
I told you I'd do it once.
A MAN OF HIS WORD
I just couldn't hold that one in.
This is making me gassy.
I haven't heard a dragon burp in so long.
-Really?
-Yes, it was a proper, long burp.
You're Byun Loong-han now.
There's no actors' facade for you to shed.
I've shed it already.
You're butt naked right now.
You're running around naked
with everything out in the open.
I want to hand you this coriander
so you can cover up.
That's a bit harsh. I was only joking.
This wouldn't cut it.
ONE BITE
HERE IT COMES AGAIN
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
The tofu one's great.
GLANCE
You don't eat much, do you?
-Me?
-You won't stuff yourself.
No, I would. But my stomach's shrunken.
Before I came here,
I lost four kilograms.
Why?
I wanted to look nice for the camera.
That's one thing I can't seem to shed.
Then you have great self-control.
It's hardest to resist food.
I have a lot of restraint.
You do?
I'm great at holding myself back.
Why didn't you show restraint
when burping?
That's something I can't do.
Okay, sorry.
I dare you to burp.
Do-yeon.
I'll hold it in with my life.
But, honestly,
please do it.
I'm serious.
I'm… sorry.
It felt like someone shot me
with an arrow.
It felt like I was hit by…
I keep hearing gas in my ear.
SOUND DIRECTOR
AFTER THE BURP FIASCO
Let's go. I'm having so much fun.
Central Street, please.
Sir.
What's famous at Central Street?
DRIVER'S RECOMMENDATION
ICE CREAM
Oh, ice cream?
CRASH COURSE ON CENTRAL STREET
Russia.
-There are a lot of Russian shops.
-A lot of Russian shops?
And a lot of Russian cuisine.
-Russian.
-Yes.
It'll remind you of your ex.
Cut. Let's do that again.
-I don't have an ex.
-Natasha.
Hey, Natasha. I miss you.
I don't have a past.
-I'm sorry.
-Today's what matters.
I think what's great about hanging out
with you is that we're so different.
It really feels like we're on a trip.
Yes, we're having so much fun
because there's no one to impress.
I still want to impress you.
Honey?
Honey.
But baribari…
I like that it means packing loads
and heading somewhere.
A lot of talk. It means
we'll bring bundles of good chat.
Right. And it sounds like bballi bballi.
-Doing something quick.
-Quick?
Let's get it. Bballi bballi.
It's all in how you frame it.
And the more we walk,
the more our bal will hurt.
"My feet hurt."
-Why do my bal hurt so much?
-My bal are killing me.
A year ago, before I met you,
around five months before,
I had a bal operation.
-Why?
-I injured my foot.
Why? While shooting?
I hurt my foot while filming.
I had an operation ten years ago,
and it flared up again.
My injury recurred. That was jae-bari.
So I needed another bal operation.
It's a little weird to say this,
but you had an injury jae-bari?
BORN TO JOIN JANGDOBARI
MR. & MRS. BARI ARE ALMOST THERE
It's been so long.
How's this place? Similar to 20 years ago?
In terms of the way it feels,
I'm not sure if it's because
I was in a dark place at the time,
but it feels brighter.
-Now?
-Yes.
Back then,
I thought this place felt quite glum.
There it is. It says "Zhongyang Street."
ZHONGYANG STREET
Thank you.
My, it's completely lit up.
We're actually at Central Street.
CENTRAL STREET
HARBIN'S RUSSIAN-INFLUENCED
TOURIST DISTRICT
All the buildings look European.
Is it like Myeong-dong?
Pretty much, yes.
A lot of foreigners come here.
Looks like it.
-That's in Russian.
-It is.
SIGNS IN RUSSIAN
-They have tanghulu.
-And matryoshka dolls!
-That's Russian, isn't it?
-It is.
-Bring up memories?
-Yes.
Of Natasha?
They're like onions.
CHANGING THE SUBJECT
-They have endless layers.
-Yes.
It's so surreal
that I'm walking this street right now.
Why? To be back somewhere
you were at years ago?
It's just weird being here with you.
I haven't even been here
with my close friends.
But I'm here with you.
Is it the same as 17 years ago?
It feels very different.
What's still the same?
Anything that hasn't changed?
Hey, Jordan!
Jordan hasn't changed.
Wow, I went there. The Air Jordan store.
-Did you buy sneakers?
-No, I didn't.
Were you too broke?
There weren't any that I liked,
and I was broke too.
Got ya.
So it's there.
Are they all lining up?
So this is the famous ice cream.
MUST-TRY ICE CREAM OF CENTRAL STREET
EVERYONE'S LOVING THE ICE CREAM
Hey, they also have tanghulu.
TANGHULU
CANDIED FRUIT
You want chocolate or milk?
MADIE'ER
HARBIN'S STAPLE ICE CREAM
I want to try the tanghulu.
Could we have one tanghulu
and one madie'er?
I'll pay.
Wow, thank you.
Cheers.
-What fruit is this?
-Twenty years ago… This?
They're small apples.
I see.
You get it, right?
It's good.
I'm out of breath. Shall we sit?
It's tart.
The sugar coat is sweet,
but they sprinkled sesame seeds.
-So it's a bit nutty?
-Yes.
I like how different it is
from the tanghulu I'm used to.
And I like that it's not too sweet.
RIGHT UP HER ALLEY
Wow, this is lovely.
TRYING TO EAT IT THIS WAY…
AND THIS WAY…
When I've eaten this much, how…
Feels like another PCR test.
What should I do?
How many PCR tests am I getting in China?
I need to get tested too.
Here goes.
YO-HAN ALSO TAKES PART
IN THE TANGHULU TEST
CLEARS IT EASILY
That was great.
How would you rate
traveling with each other?
As travel buddies? Travel mates?
Come on.
One hundred, of course.
Out of?
Out of 950.
100 OUT OF 950…!
Make up the remaining 850 tomorrow, okay?
-Understood.
-I'm kidding.
Out of 100, of course.
There's no one like him.
The excitement and anticipation
were outweighed
by how worried I was for this trip,
but I have no worries now.
Tomorrow will be fun.
Did I make you blush today?
Me? Of course you did.
How could I not?
I tried to be
as nonchalant as I could today.
-Why's that?
-But I felt things traveling with you.
I felt relief,
and I'm just having such a great time.
Everything's perfect.
What's so funny?
How did you eat this?
Did you pierce the back of your throat?
Let me check.
Is the back of your throat… What's this?
There's a massive hole!
This is…
IS MY NECK OKAY?
Oh, there's…
I think I pierced it.
TRAVEL BUDDIES GET FULL MARKS FOR HUMOR
Where would I find
such a hilarious travel buddy?
I was asking myself how I ate it,
and I've honestly forgotten.
I guess I just shoved it in.
Let's swap now.
Sorry, I ate almost all of it.
It's down to the stick.
I'm sorry.
YUM
-What do you want to do tomorrow?
-Tomorrow?
We didn't get to drink Harbin beer today,
so I'd like to go to the museum.
How about you?
I'll just follow you.
I'd also like to drink Harbin beer
at the museum.
And?
The Harbin Institute of Technology,
the school I attended.
-I'd like to look around.
-Right, sounds good.
-Harbin's also famous for guobaorou.
-Right.
-How's that sound?
-Good.
Today will be another jam-packed day.
I'll just eat these three apples
before we go.
RESUMES THE TANGHULU TEST
SHE'S NOT VOMITING
It's so childish but hilarious.
I love this sort of stuff.
-You do? That's good.
-Yes.
Just leave me one.
-Of these? Okay.
-Yes.
You eat them and leave me one.
CRUNCH
Eat it.
HOLD THIS, PLEASE
WHATEVER YOU DO, I DO TOO
BONDING THROUGH CHOKING
Can you edit it
so it's like we're in a rom-com?
Sure, why not?
-Was that too high-pitched?
-Yes.
"Can you edit…"
"Can you edit it
so it's like we're in a rom-com?"
ASK AND YOU SHALL RECEIVE
What should I call you?
Nuna?
Nuna. Did I make you blush today?
I'll follow you, Nuna.
SHE STARTED OFF AS HIS NUNA
-Why are you doing that?
-Gen Z.
-Gen Zs post like this?
-Yes.
It truly feels like I'm on holiday.
It's so surreal
that I'm walking this street right now.
THEN THE TWO GROW CLOSER
Be careful. Come here.
When I meet you,
I think all my senses come to life.
Honey?
ONCE SHE STARTED TO OPEN HER HEART
Thank you so much, honey.
NUNA SOON BECAME HONEY
WHILE TRAVELING,
THE PAIR RUB OFF ON ONE ANOTHER
I'm already excited.
I don't think I'll be able to sleep.
AND SO WE BECAME HONEY
Tomorrow, I'll come to you
a little less carefully.
Me too.
I practiced saying good night.
Can I try it?
-Please.
-Good night.
-Hey.
-That's it, right?
-Good night.
HANDS CLASPED
Now, let's go.
RELUCTANT TO LET GO
-Let's go.
-I thought you'd be staying here.
I thought this was Will You Be There.
This was fun.
BYE
WHAT MIGHT THEY GET UP TO TOMORROW…?
-I'll try to be less careful tomorrow.
-Me too.
I'll give you this.
COOKIE-BARI
TOUCHED
-I'm not cold at all.
-Really?
You look pretty cold.
I'M FREEZING
I'm just joking.
Wear mine.
THERE'S NO NEED
I told you I was just joking.
I'm not cold at all.
-Please.
-Let's switch.
NOT A BAD SHOUT
That suits you so well.
I'm sure you'll suit that too.
YO-HAN LOOKS DAPPER IN DO-YEON'S JACKET
Let's go.
SWEET
You're Tang Wei now.
AND SO THEY RETURNED SAFELY TO THEIR HOTEL